[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Paul, from everything we're gleaning from all this, from the eyewitness accounts, the encounter with random strangers, from the car, et cetera, we clearly think they are in that vicinity but do we think they are there together as sometime of couple, that they may have established a relationship?", "question_tokens": ["Paul", ",", "from", "everything", "we", "'re", "gleaning", "from", "all", "this", ",", "from", "the", "eyewitness", "accounts", ",", "the", "encounter", "with", "random", "strangers", ",", "from", "the", "car", ",", "et", "cetera", ",", "we", "clearly", "think", "they", "are", "in", "that", "vicinity", "but", "do", "we", "think", "they", "are", "there", "together", "as", "sometime", "of", "couple", ",", "that", "they", "may", "have", "established", "a", "relationship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, I pressed the sheriff on that very question, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "pressed", "the", "sheriff", "on", "that", "very", "question", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Does that matter at this time of year or can you survive quite easily, given it's pretty warm?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "matter", "at", "this", "time", "of", "year", "or", "can", "you", "survive", "quite", "easily", ",", "given", "it", "'s", "pretty", "warm", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well, we don't -- right, we don't have any of the extreme temperatures, however, again, I mean, this is not -- you're not going to have easy access to food in this area.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "--", "right", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "have", "any", "of", "the", "extreme", "temperatures", ",", "however", ",", "again", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "this", "is", "not", "--", "you", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "have", "easy", "access", "to", "food", "in", "this", "area", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI", "FBI"], "PERSON": ["Laura Robinson"]}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Well, first, I'd like to say that the information I am about to tell you, I've already notified the FBI about three hours ago when I became aware of it and told the FBI which I got directly from Laura Robinson.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", ",", "I", "'d", "like", "to", "say", "that", "the", "information", "I", "am", "about", "to", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "'ve", "already", "notified", "the", "FBI", "about", "three", "hours", "ago", "when", "I", "became", "aware", "of", "it", "and", "told", "the", "FBI", "which", "I", "got", "directly", "from", "Laura", "Robinson", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "JJR", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Can he survive pretty easily in that kind of terrain from your experience?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "he", "survive", "pretty", "easily", "in", "that", "kind", "of", "terrain", "from", "your", "experience", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "No, and that's one of the things that, you know, has got me more concerned with a small backpack they are looking at several days of being in the woods.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "has", "got", "me", "more", "concerned", "with", "a", "small", "backpack", "they", "are", "looking", "at", "several", "days", "of", "being", "in", "the", "woods", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "But given what you know now, do you fear that you may have been too optimistic in terms of believing he may be an innocent victim?", "question_tokens": ["But", "given", "what", "you", "know", "now", ",", "do", "you", "fear", "that", "you", "may", "have", "been", "too", "optimistic", "in", "terms", "of", "believing", "he", "may", "be", "an", "innocent", "victim", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "I wouldn't say I was defensive or optimistic.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "say", "I", "was", "defensive", "or", "optimistic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hannah"]}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Was she unnerved by it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "unnerved", "by", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Oh, yes, definitely, as well as me and Hannah were.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "definitely", ",", "as", "well", "as", "me", "and", "Hannah", "were", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "In terms of what she said to you about James DiMaggio, is it possible at all do you think that she could have gone off with him willingly?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "what", "she", "said", "to", "you", "about", "James", "DiMaggio", ",", "is", "it", "possible", "at", "all", "do", "you", "think", "that", "she", "could", "have", "gone", "off", "with", "him", "willingly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James DiMaggio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Idaho"]}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Is it possible, Alan, that Hannah may be totally unaware about what happened to her mother and to her brother and this and that she's absconded with this man and gone on some crazy adventure completely unaware about what he's done?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "possible", ",", "Alan", ",", "that", "Hannah", "may", "be", "totally", "unaware", "about", "what", "happened", "to", "her", "mother", "and", "to", "her", "brother", "and", "this", "and", "that", "she", "'s", "absconded", "with", "this", "man", "and", "gone", "on", "some", "crazy", "adventure", "completely", "unaware", "about", "what", "he", "'s", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "She may be unaware of her mother and brother's death, but I feel like even if she is, she knows something is wrong because she would never go off to Idaho and across four states with him, without knowing anything.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "may", "be", "unaware", "of", "her", "mother", "and", "brother", "'s", "death", ",", "but", "I", "feel", "like", "even", "if", "she", "is", ",", "she", "knows", "something", "is", "wrong", "because", "she", "would", "never", "go", "off", "to", "Idaho", "and", "across", "four", "states", "with", "him", ",", "without", "knowing", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan", "Hannah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "EX", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", ":", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "I mean, Hannah, what would you say James DiMaggio is like from what she's told you and what you may have seen and heard yourself?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Hannah", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "James", "DiMaggio", "is", "like", "from", "what", "she", "'s", "told", "you", "and", "what", "you", "may", "have", "seen", "and", "heard", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Well, he was -- he was a very nice person that you could easily get along with and he was just always there for Hannah for anything and just -- just a really nice sensitive person, I guess, you would say.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "was", "--", "he", "was", "a", "very", "nice", "person", "that", "you", "could", "easily", "get", "along", "with", "and", "he", "was", "just", "always", "there", "for", "Hannah", "for", "anything", "and", "just", "--", "just", "a", "really", "nice", "sensitive", "person", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "you", "would", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hannah", "James DiMaggio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "And, finally, Alan, if by any chance Hannah is near a television and may see this now or when we repeat the show later, what would you say to her?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "finally", ",", "Alan", ",", "if", "by", "any", "chance", "Hannah", "is", "near", "a", "television", "and", "may", "see", "this", "now", "or", "when", "we", "repeat", "the", "show", "later", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Just that, I mean, we're looking for her and we came across his car and that we are looking for her.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "that", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "we", "'re", "looking", "for", "her", "and", "we", "came", "across", "his", "car", "and", "that", "we", "are", "looking", "for", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan", "Hannah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Do you think he planned it because of the psychological trauma perhaps of his death?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "planned", "it", "because", "of", "the", "psychological", "trauma", "perhaps", "of", "his", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Well, let's get real here, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "get", "real", "here", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hannah"]}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Given the fact that we have an eyewitness now, who was on horseback and claimed to see them and saw no sign of unwillingness on the part of the woman that he believed to be young Hannah and the fact that the investigators saying the fire and kidnapping seem to be a very well-planned event, can we rule out, John, despite the father's understandable total distress and desperation to get her back, can we rule out, given all that, that Hannah may be completely unaware of what he did to her brother and her mother, and that she may have gone on what she believed to be just an adventure with this man?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "the", "fact", "that", "we", "have", "an", "eyewitness", "now", ",", "who", "was", "on", "horseback", "and", "claimed", "to", "see", "them", "and", "saw", "no", "sign", "of", "unwillingness", "on", "the", "part", "of", "the", "woman", "that", "he", "believed", "to", "be", "young", "Hannah", "and", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "investigators", "saying", "the", "fire", "and", "kidnapping", "seem", "to", "be", "a", "very", "well-planned", "event", ",", "can", "we", "rule", "out", ",", "John", ",", "despite", "the", "father", "'s", "understandable", "total", "distress", "and", "desperation", "to", "get", "her", "back", ",", "can", "we", "rule", "out", ",", "given", "all", "that", ",", "that", "Hannah", "may", "be", "completely", "unaware", "of", "what", "he", "did", "to", "her", "brother", "and", "her", "mother", ",", "and", "that", "she", "may", "have", "gone", "on", "what", "she", "believed", "to", "be", "just", "an", "adventure", "with", "this", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "DT", ",", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Well, let's hope that's the case, but no one, unless -- until the story is over and no one who has walked in the shoes of Hannah, unless they have walked in those shoes, has any right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "hope", "that", "'s", "the", "case", ",", "but", "no", "one", ",", "unless", "--", "until", "the", "story", "is", "over", "and", "no", "one", "who", "has", "walked", "in", "the", "shoes", "of", "Hannah", ",", "unless", "they", "have", "walked", "in", "those", "shoes", ",", "has", "any", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hannah", "John", "Hannah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Do you believe that that is a good positive sign that he hasn't gone away and just killed her?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "that", "is", "a", "good", "positive", "sign", "that", "he", "has", "n't", "gone", "away", "and", "just", "killed", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "ALSH: No, absolutely, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["ALSH", ":", "No", ",", "absolutely", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tameka Foster Raymond"]}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "That's pretty unusual for a mother not to get custody at all in that kind of case, and that probably explains her desperation to try and resolve that today using the swimming pool incident as an excuse?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "pretty", "unusual", "for", "a", "mother", "not", "to", "get", "custody", "at", "all", "in", "that", "kind", "of", "case", ",", "and", "that", "probably", "explains", "her", "desperation", "to", "try", "and", "resolve", "that", "today", "using", "the", "swimming", "pool", "incident", "as", "an", "excuse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Yes, we don't know exactly why it is Tameka Foster Raymond did not get custody of the two boys.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "exactly", "why", "it", "is", "Tameka", "Foster", "Raymond", "did", "not", "get", "custody", "of", "the", "two", "boys", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Is she going to carry on trying to get custody, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "going", "to", "carry", "on", "trying", "to", "get", "custody", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "She is going to carry on.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "is", "going", "to", "carry", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Will this become something that we see in real life?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "this", "become", "something", "that", "we", "see", "in", "real", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "There is another question --", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "another", "question", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "This is in England?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "in", "England", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "You can do the weather here in New York.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "do", "the", "weather", "here", "in", "New", "York", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "This is the stuff of madness, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "stuff", "of", "madness", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "No, this is exactly what makes the NRA and its supporters look insane.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "this", "is", "exactly", "what", "makes", "the", "NRA", "and", "its", "supporters", "look", "insane", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Newtown"]}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "I mean, what is the mentality of people marching down to their Starbucks which sells coffee, and taking their firearms to make some fatuous point, in a place that's been desecrated by gun violence?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "is", "the", "mentality", "of", "people", "marching", "down", "to", "their", "Starbucks", "which", "sells", "coffee", ",", "and", "taking", "their", "firearms", "to", "make", "some", "fatuous", "point", ",", "in", "a", "place", "that", "'s", "been", "desecrated", "by", "gun", "violence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Well, I didn't agree with the Newtown march.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "agree", "with", "the", "Newtown", "march", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "What about that right?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "That is where the Constitution comes in, you don't get to impose your view of the Second Amendment on your fellow citizens if your state has decided that those citizens can carry concealed weapons.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "where", "the", "Constitution", "comes", "in", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "get", "to", "impose", "your", "view", "of", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "on", "your", "fellow", "citizens", "if", "your", "state", "has", "decided", "that", "those", "citizens", "can", "carry", "concealed", "weapons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "They can't go into a Starbucks and get a coffee like you can?", "question_tokens": ["They", "ca", "n't", "go", "into", "a", "Starbucks", "and", "get", "a", "coffee", "like", "you", "can", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"]}}]